const quizData = [
    {
        question: 'What is the capital of United Kingdom?',
        options: ['London', 'Paris', 'England', 'France'],
        answer: 'London'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the Prime Minister of United Kingdom ?',
        options: ['rishi sunak', 'liz truss', 'boris johnson', 'theresa may'],
        answer: 'rishi sunak'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the national animal of United kingdom?',
        options: ['Tiger', 'Lion', 'Elephant', 'Leopard'],
        answer: 'lion'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the national bird of United kingdom?',
        options: ['europesn robin', 'Sparrow', 'Pigeon', 'Eagle'],
        answer: 'european robin'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the national sport of United kingdom?',
        options: ['Cricket', 'Hockey', 'Football', 'Kabaddi'],
        answer: 'football'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the current monarch of united kingdom?',
        options: ['queen elizabeth', 'king charles', 'prince william', 'king george'],
        answer: 'queen elizabeth'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the longest river in the united kingdom',
        options: ['severn', 'thames', 'clyde', 'mersy'],
        answer: 'severn'
    },
    {
        question: 'In which year did the united kingdom vote to leave the european union?',
        options: ['2016', '2012', '2007', '2010'],
        answer: '2016'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these is the official currency of united kingdom?',
        options: ['euro', 'pound sterling', 'dollar', 'franc'],
        answer: 'pound sterling'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these countries is not part of united kingdom?',
        options: ['england', 'scotland', 'wales', 'ireland'],
        answer: 'ireland'
    }
];

export default quizData;